<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Neha Chaudhary</title>
    <link>https://neha-2896.github.io/neha_portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Neha Chaudhary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://neha-2896.github.io/neha_portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>StackSample: 10% of Stack Overflow Q&amp;A</title>
      <link>https://neha-2896.github.io/neha_portfolio/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neha-2896.github.io/neha_portfolio/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Stackoverflow follows a ‘Question and Answer’ format and there are strict standards on the manner in which users can interact on the forum. Stackoverflow forum is used for many purposes including:
 Getting solutions to programming problems; Gaining generic information on programming languages and; Learning new concepts in programming.  Dataset : https://www.kaggle.com/stackoverflow/stacksample
In this project I tried to build a semantic search engine in which returns top 10 similar questions and top 10 relevant answers for the query or question asked by user within some milliseconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Malware Classification Challenge</title>
      <link>https://neha-2896.github.io/neha_portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neha-2896.github.io/neha_portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>The term malware is a contraction of malicious software. Put simply, malware is any piece of software that was written with the intent of doing harm to data, devices or to people. In the past few years, the malware industry has grown very rapidly that, the syndicates invest heavily in technologies to evade traditional protection, forcing the anti-malware groups/communities to build more robust softwares to detect and terminate these attacks. The goal is protecting a computer system from a malware attack is to identify whether a given piece of file/software is a malware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Network Graph Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://neha-2896.github.io/neha_portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neha-2896.github.io/neha_portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>The goal of the project is, given a directed social graph, have to predict missing links to recommend users (Link Prediction in graph).
Dataset : https://www.kaggle.com/c/FacebookRecruiting/data Data contains two columns source and destination edge in graph.
First map the problem statement to suprevised learning problem. Generated training samples of good and bad links from given directed graph and for each link got some features like no of followers, is he followed back, page rank, katz score, adar index, some svd fetures of adj matrix, some weight features etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DonorsChoose.org Application Screening</title>
      <link>https://neha-2896.github.io/neha_portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neha-2896.github.io/neha_portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>DonorsChoose.org receives hundreds of thousands of project proposals each year for classroom projects in need of funding. Right now, a large number of volunteers is needed to manually screen each submission before it&amp;rsquo;s approved to be posted on the DonorsChoose.org website.
The goal of the project is to predict whether or not a DonorsChoose.org project proposal submitted by a teacher will be approved or not.
Dataset : https://www.kaggle.com/c/donorschoose-application-screening/data</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
